searchenginestrategies.de 2007-12-23

# Incisive Media - Privacy Policy

**Information Collection and Use**  
Incisive Media  is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties in ways other than those disclosed in this policy. Incisive Media  collects information from our users at several different points on our websites. 

Incisive Media includes Incisive Media and all of its subsidiary companies (Incisive Financial Publishing Limited, Incisive Photographic Limited, Global Professional Media Limited, Conjecture Limited, Incisive Media Investments Limited, Incisive RWG Inc, Incisive Interactive Marketing LLC).

**Registration**  
some of our sites restrict access to online content. To gain entry a user must first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and e-mail address). For sites where online access to content is part of a subscription package, registration forms will often contain full subscriber details used to identify and fulfil that subscriber's account. 

**E-mail alerts**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our alerts, updates, briefings etc. we ask for contact and delivery information such as name and e-mail address. All of these e-mail lists provide opt out facilities online and with each e-mail broadcast. In some cases the user is asked to provide optional demographic and personal interest information that is used to keep our content as relevant as possible. 

**Sharing**  
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We would also share information when using an outside shipping company to ship orders or a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services.

On some sites, which generate reports from directories and listings, we share the names and e-mail addresses of an individual user with some of companies whose products and services are mentioned within that report. Where this occurs there is an opt out provided if a user does not wish to receive any contact from those companies.

**Orders**  
We request information from the user on our order forms. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfil customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. All online transactions are processed using SSL encryption (see Security for more detail)

**Cookies**  
Many of our sites use cookies - A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of cookies is for the convenience of visitors. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users in order to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to, or control over, these cookies.

**Clear Gifs**  
We employ a software technology called clear gifs (also known as Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are not tied to users' personally identifiable information. In addition, we use clear gifs in our HTML-based e-mails to let us know which e-mails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. All of our e-mail newsletters provide the facility to opt-out (see opt-out section below). 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track a user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Links**  
Some of our websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Incisive Media is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website. 

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time to time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Recommend this site**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and e-mail address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the site. This information is not stored except for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail.

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

**Special Offers**  
On some sites new members receive a welcome e-mail to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Where this is the case we present the option to not receive these types of communications at the point of sign up. 

**Site and Service Updates**  
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via e-mail or phone. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done at the registration page or by e-mailing the site editor. Many of our sites will offer subscribers an account management facility that will allow them to change or amend their own records.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive a newsletter/alert/briefing etc. may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to the unsubscribe link in the e-mail or online. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will seek to advise all users of these changes.

**Discussion boards:**

While we take every precaution to ensure all contributions to discussion boards are factually correct, and not deemed to be untruthful, libellous, defamatory, racist or persecutory, these messages are entered by third parties. All users of the board are presented with a set of house rules before taking part. Our editor will monitor as much as possible and although all users of the site are entitled to their opinion, language on the boards must be clean - contributions containing sexual swear words and slander will be removed. Users will be warned if breaking the house rules. A user who consistently breaks the house rules will be barred from the discussion boards`. All users are reminded of copyright - Articles from other websites should be linked to rather than copied in full. Articles from within Incisive Media  publications/websites may be copied in their entirety for use on Incisive Media  discussion boards. Incisive Media  reserves the right to remove articles without notice or reason.
